Let me also take a moment. Anybody here who is self-conscious about your fupa? You know that
that piece of the abdomen right there? Anybody here who's self-conscious about that? Please let
it go. Please. And I know that you may not want to admit it, but a lot of us are self-conscious
about that because we think it's unattractive. We think men don't like it, you know? We think
it looks bad in clothes. And I just want to remind you, men who like women like fupas, okay?
Men who like women like fupas because women have fupas. I'm going to say that again. Men
who like women like fupas. So that's what this picture should tell you because that's a manly
hand holding a womanly fupa. And I said, we're going to take this picture so that I can have
this conversation because I know it needs to be had because I know how many of us
really do feel some type of way about this natural abdomen experience. So shout out to
all of us, particularly us in perimenopause, particularly the moms who have had kids,
particularly the women who have had hysterectomies and don't have the muscle there. So it's just
literally fat and there's nothing you can fucking do about it. Like we got to flip that. Those with
the fibroids, taking up space, embrace your fupa. It's an acronym. Is it? What's the acronym
stand for? Fat upper pussy area. Great. So big ups to all of us with our fat, big ups to all of us with
our fat upper pussy areas and big up to all the men who understand, appreciate, and love
that we possess them. Because at the end of the day, just embrace you. Embrace you. Now don't be
on no bullshit where you're being unhealthy, but embrace you and embrace you. Men who like women
like fupas. I think I'm gonna make a shirt.